Alaeldin Musa Full Stack Developer

+971588530119

Q Dubai



Skills

jira trello

SKIII3		
Core Php • • • • •	SDLC	• • • • •
object Oriented Programming	Design Pattern	• • • • •
Database Management $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ MSql ,Oracle,Postgres Monogo Database	RESTful API Design	• • • • •
Laravel • • • • •	JetStream	• • • • •
Laravel Lumen	Ajax	• • • •
Security • • • • • • • • HTTPS, SSL/TLS	GitHub Azure And Aws	
Integration with other System • • • • •	Mvvm	• • • • •
Fire Base Real Time Database/Fire Base Authentication/Fire Base Messaging/Fire Base Ui	Mvc	• • • • •
MicroService Archicture/Monolitic ● ● ● ● ● MicroService	Solid Principle	• • • • •
	html	• • • • •
Testing $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ JUnit and Integration Testing Mockito	Java Script	• • • • •
Design Pattern • • • • • •	Angular	• • • • •
Factory Singelton ,Observer	Collaboration Tools JIRA	• • • •
Clean Code Archictur ● ● ● ● ● Mvc,Mvvm	•	
Css/BootStrap	Testing Domain Driven TDD	••••
Jquery • • • • •	User Interface (UI) Rendering Retrofit/WebSocket	• • • • •
Google Map Api ● ● ● ●	Data Binding	• • • • •
Domain-Driven Design (DDD) • • • • •		
SoftSkills Adaptability and flexibility Problem-solving and critical thinking Time management and multitasking Problem Solving Communication Team Collaboration		
User Interaction Handling ● ● ● ●		
Project Management		

Talented Web Developer with over 6+ years of software and web development experience in a broad range of industries, including sports entertainment, restaurant management. Solid understanding of full web and software development life cycles, UIX, web analytics, changing web standards, and Agile methodologies. Dedicated to continuously developing, implementing, and adopting new technologies to maximize development efficiency and produce innovative applications.

Professional Experience

2023/05 - 2023/11

Full Stack Developer

Dubai, United Emirates

Mod Soft

Collaborated with stakeholders to gather and analyze project requirements, ensuring clarity and feasibility. Developed comprehensive system design plans, including architecture, database structure, and UI/UX considerations. Oversaw coding and implementation phases, ensuring adherence to project requirements and design specifications. Established rigorous testing protocols to verify the functionality, reliability, and security of software products. Coordinated the deployment process, ensuring a seamless transition from development to production. Built the application backend using Laravel and the front end using Angular.

2022/12 - 2023/04 Khartoum, Sudan

Full Stack developer

Aurgus Company

Managing the complete software development process from conception to deployment

Maintaining and upgrading the software following deployment

Managing the end-to-end life cycle for the production of software and application Overseeing and guiding the analyzing, writing, building, and deployment of software Overseeing the automated testing and providing feedback to management

- during the development process
- Modifying and testing changes to previously developed programs

2022/05 - 2022/12

Software Developer

AbuDahbi,

Hmc Infotech

United Arab Emirates

I Execute full Software development life cycle (SDLC) I Write well-designed, testable code Produce specifications and determine operational feasibility Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing systems Create project using Php and Laravel Framework. Using Hibernate and Elquent and

2020/01 - 2022/04 Khartoum.

Full Stack Developer

XIIai touiii,

City Soft Company

United Arab Emirates

Developed an auction software for crops exchanges and selling. Test applications prior to final review to ensure that all issues were resolved in the most efficient manner.

Created custom mobile applications using native technologies as per client specifications.

Provided dedicated support and timely issue resolution to clients following successful app launch.

Devised all documentation for each app, detailing all aspects, functions, capabilities and features.

Provided a weekly progress report to the executive staff, ensuring that all parties were informed of milestones.

 $\ensuremath{\mathbb{I}}$ Created responsive front-end for web and mobile applications interfaces according to design guidelines and information

architecture.

Designed, tested, and implemented components when creating cutting-edge digital solutions.

UN Worked closely with other developers, UX designers, business and systems analysts to create cohesively finished [bursa exchange, health insurance].

□ Identified areas for modification in existing programs, developing modifications to suit business and product requirements. Wrote and implemented efficient [Java] code, guaranteeing business needs were effectively met.

Urote clean code to develop fully functional applications. Designed, tested and implemented components when creating cutting-edge digital solutions.

Championed small details and creative solutions to add value for customers.

2018/01 - 2019/12

full Stack Developer

Sudan, Khartoum

Robotic Company

Worked as a full stack developer and participated in analyzing and developing applications in many sectors with different business backgrounds such as booking services, ERP, ecommerce, teaching, and payment gateways.

2017/01 – 2018/11 Khartoum, Sudan

Full Stack Developer

Kushite Company

Managing the complete software development process from conception to deployment

Maintaining and upgrading the software following deployment

Managing the end-to-end life cycle for the production of software and application

Overseeing and guiding the analyzing, writing, building, and deployment of software

Overseeing the automated testing and providing feedback to management during the

development process

Modifying and testing changes to previously developed programs

Languages

Arabic

English

Native

Education

2012/12 - 2016/12

Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Information Technology

Khartoum, sudan

Sudan Unversity

Nationality

• Sudanese